They say we are "cursed children,"
because at birth, we possess the
cursed power to control magical beasts.
You worthless brats...
I heard that a long, long time ago,
it was an ability
that only controlled livestock,
but then someone started using it
to control monsters in war
and killed a lot of people,
so we became loathed.
I told you not to look at me
with those nasty eyes.
We were hit, kicked...
Being sent flying by a kick
was a daily occurrence.
Why...
do you beat me?
I'll tell you when you can speak!
When I asked a question once,
I was beaten until
I was almost unrecognizable,
and I only got water
with no food for three whole days.
Maybe because of the cursed power,
I happened to be able to read
the minds of anyone in front of me.
So that thing is demon folk...
Maybe it's one of them who killed Mom!
It's probably thinking of how to
exterminate us humans!
Maybe it's one of them who killed Mom!
It's probably thinking of how to
exterminate us humans!
I'm so angry!
It should have been that bastard!
When they knew that
I could read their minds,
they got even more violent.
It can read minds? How frightening!
This is why I hate them!
Useless wretch!
Scum!
Just die!
You filthy vermin!
But no matter what
awful things happened to me,
I never retaliated,
and I never even thought of doing so.
Even though I hated that I was loathed,
abused, and beaten,
I never even wanted
to think about hurting anyone else.
More than anything,
I just didn't want to see any more blood.
However...
You can help a certain country
by taking these monsters with you.
Demon folk can be useful to people...
no, the nation.
What could bring you more pride?
I can be useful to people?
If you simply do as I say,
you will never be beaten
for no reason again.
I will let you eat your fill
of delicious meals.
And not just you, that goes
for everyone here.
I promise.
But if you turn it down,
you'll get the same treatment.
Or rather, your days will be full
of even more pain than they are now.
Because he wore a magical device
on his forehead,
I couldn't read his mind.
But that man always kept his promises.
That's why...
Since he promised me...
I have to kill them...
I have to-
The seal!
I can't control it anymore!
I've messed up...
Oh, no...
Everyone's going to suffer again
because of me...
I'm sorry.
But... now it can just kill me.
I helped no one and nothing,
but I didn't hurt anyone.
I am happy to die here.
If I'm reborn, I hope I won't
get beaten so badly in my next life.
I hope I can be at least
a little bit useful to someone.
And I hope I can have something
delicious to eat, at least once.
Parry!
Why...
Why is this person protecting me?
Oh no!
Huh? The bleeding stopped...
That's good...
I can make this work out after all.
Dad. Mom.
I'm going to go gather
some ingredients in the mountains.
It all started a short while
after I returned from the training schools
in the royal capital, at dinner time.
I got a whole lot today!
I'll dry these outside.
And I'll pickle these.
And the rest...
I guess I'll stick them in a soup.
Yummy!
Even if there was
something inedible in there,
I thought it would just give me
a bit of a stomachache.
But it was highly poisonous.
This is bad...
Low... Heal...
This is it...
Dragon's Ruin.
Mom told me never to eat this one.
I still have work to do.
Low Heal.
It doesn't hurt...
Am I better?
I'm so hungry.
Dragon's Ruin.
I have to be care-
A Poison Spike!
I think... it also had...
It was highly poisonous.
Huh... I feel all right.
If I'm okay eating poison,
maybe I can eat this too.
I don't believe it!
This is incredibly delicious!
The poison is spreading
slower than yesterday.
I gained some tolerance.
All right!
This might lead to me
acquiring a new skill!
From then on I developed
a taste for poisonous things.
I'd collapse on occasion.
In the end I didn't acquire any skills,
but I could eat poisonous things at the
cost of vomiting a small amount of blood.
Gosh, I can't believe
poisonous creatures are this yummy!
What a discovery!
And that's probably why...
this thing is also delicious.
Instructor!
At first,
I couldn't counteract the poison in time,
so I spewed a little bit of blood,
but I know from experience,
that much is no big deal.
Is the kid okay?
It seems like the detoxification
of my Low Heal took effect in time.
Parry!
Wow...
He can take on
such a horrible monster by himself?!
Parry!
That's huge.
I guess this is the
frog's all-or-nothing death strike.
But...
Parry!
This sure is awful.
Strange that such a huge and
dangerous frog is outside the city.
But even so, this poisonous of a frog
is probably pretty tasty.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Uh, he's not looking too good.
I'll have Lynne look him over later.
That really was a close one.
Did you come here all by yourself?
Um... well, no.
Oh?
I'm the one who brought that thing here.
B-because I promised...
to bring it to the city.
To the city? He promised?
He went through all that trouble
to bring that poison frog there?
He can't mean...
That HAS to be it!
That frog...
must've been for eating, huh?!
Well, if you're trying to deliver
that much fresh meat,
getting it there while alive
is the best way to do it, for sure.
I understand he had
to use seal to hide himself
to be safe and not get robbed,
and it's not surprising that a large city
would also have the techniques
to manage that poison properly.
Maybe this kid even put in a lot of work
to raise this frog the best he could...
Yeah, grow up strong and healthy!
Good boy, good boy, good boy!
Such a good boy!
I ruined the delivery
of his precious stock to the city!
I'm sorry I did this
to your valuable food supply!
Huh?!
I'll pay for it.
I don't have much money, though,
so it'll take me some time!
Uh, no...
You don't have to pay me for it.
But...
It's really okay, don't worry!
Are you sure?
It's in so many pieces now...
Okay, then.
But, how did you bring
that ferocious creature this far?
There's no way
you could have dragged it here.
I-I can control monsters.
I used that to bring it all the way here.
Wh-what do you mean
you can control monsters?!
This tiny kid can control
that enormous monster?
What an amazing skill.
Are there others in the world
that can do that sort of thing?
Huh? Skill?
Is it not one?
I was born with it...
It's that sort of power.
B-born with it?!
Being able to do that
from the day you were born...
Impressive.
Something like that can only be
a talent gifted from the heavens.
U-um...
I'm de-
demon folk, so...
Demon folk?
Yeah.
All demon folk can do that sort of thing.
Ah, so basically demon folk
are a tribe who all have that ability,
and it's nothing special, right?
Yeah.
I've imagined so many times
about what I'd do if I had that ability...
I'd have animals help
work the fields and stuff.
If I can use birds, it'd be nice
to have them deliver letters.
Even at night, I wouldn't worry about
getting attacked by stray dogs.
That's seriously impressive.
U-um, you aren't afraid of me
being demon folk?
You don't... hate me?
What do you mean?
There are people who are scared of,
and also hate that I have, this power.
Who would hate a power like that?
Well, I don't think it's something you
should pay much mind to, you know?
They can say what they want,
but that's a super useful ability.
Useful?
Me, really?
Of course!
That's how great of a skill it is.
I wish I could take it off your hands.
R-really?
Can someone...
like me really be needed?
Unlike me, he was blessed
with a desirable ability,
so why does he have so little self-worth?
He's probably focused
on other things right now,
but I'm sure this kid will go places.
Of course.
Way more than they'd need me.
Hordes of them would,
if that's what you want.
Instructor!
Are you all right?
Yes, completely fine.
I must treat you immediately.
Nah, I'm really okay.
I'm not even bleeding anymore.
Not to brag,
but I'm strong against poison.
It makes no sense...
That wasn't just deadly poison...
That was a miasma, I'm sure of it.
An extreme poison
that even ruins the soil in its path.
Taking that direct attack and then
carrying on as if nothing has happened...
No, there's one possibility.
"Sacred Spirit."
Instructor Sain the Sovereign of Salvation
once showed it to me.
By honing the body and mind
like a saint,
the technique purifies
everything it touches
and heals all wounds...
It is the perfection he finally found
at the end of his unconventional training.
It took Instructor Sain 40 years,
but Instructor Noor achieved it
while still so young?
Oh yeah, Lynne,
please tend to this kid first.
I-I'm fine.
I don't need help either.
Pale skin.
Hair of silver mixed with light blue.
Dark eyes that seem like they'll
pull you into their depths...
I knew it.
Are you a demon folk child?
Yeah, demon folk.
You know your stuff!
Even knowing this,
Instructor, will this child-
Uh, what do you intend to do?
If I can, I want to take him
in the carriage...
Sir Noor, you can't-
We can't?
They are a dangerous race which
many countries recommended killing...
Are you really okay with that, Instructor?
This child is demon folk, and the monster
it brought along caused this situation...
It sure is unfortunate that
the wheat field got messed up...
but he can't finish his job with
the poison frog because of me.
By "poison frog" do you mean
that Black Death Dragon?!
You were bringing a
Black Death Dragon to the city?!
This is far too dangerous,
like I thought!
Even if he is just a child.
So you said you promised to do all that,
but who asked you to?
I don't know.
They wouldn't tell me.
Concealing the truth will do you no good.
It would be a huge help
if you told us the truth.
I really don't know.
I was raised this way.
The frightened demeanor
and look in his eyes...
It's clear as day.
This child is a slave.
Slaves are outlawed in the Clays Kingdom,
but that isn't the case
in other countries.
In all likelihood, he's a child soldier
whose status is being taken advantage of.
Do you have a home to go back to?
Well, I was blindfolded part
of the way here,
and I don't know where
the city I was in might be.
Then what do you think about this?
I'd like to give you
a ride to the nearest city.
What was I looking at?
My father often warned me not to be misled
by rumors and trust my own eyes,
but I only saw a boy from
a "wicked race" that scared me.
I didn't see him as a malnourished child
with nowhere to go.
I'm so ashamed of myself
for being small-minded.
Now then, what's your name?
Rolo.
Rolo, huh? Great name.
Short and easy to remember.
Ines...
I also have a favor to ask of you.
Can we take this child, Rolo, with us?
Lady Lynneburg.
I understand how you feel.
However...
If there's no room for him,
he can have my spot.
That isn't the problem.
Demon folk are not allowed entry
into the Holy Theocracy of Mithra,
which is our destination.
It may be difficult to bring him with us.
Likewise, even if we leave him
on the way there,
it would be difficult
for this boy to survive alone.
I understand that.
If we bring him with us,
we may be considered
enemies of Mithra and attacked.
Even so, I...
This is unexpected.
Huh, I thought it'd be
long dead by now.
#6 I Parry Deadly Poison